

HOANG PHI HUNG

Frontend Developer



31/03/1999



0395713199



hunghoang.310399@gmail.com



48A Duong Thi Muoi, Tan Chanh Hiep , D.12 , HCM city



https://www.linkedin.com/in/hunghoang310399/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Strongest Areas

Data Structures, Algorithms

Programming Languages

Javascript, C#, Java

Libraries/Frameworks

React.js, Express.js, Next.js, Typescript, Springboot, Git, Node.js,Docker

Database

MySQL, SQLServer, MongoDB, Firebase, PostgreSQL

Platforms

Azure, Vercel, AWS

HONORS & AWARDS

2019

Van Lang Creative Idea Contest won a consolation prize

2019

Top 10 APKATHON contests 2019

2020

Front-end programmer with 5 years of experience in developing web interfaces using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6+), React and Redux. The goal is to apply these skills to create a good and effective user experience.

EDUCATION



Van Lang University | SEP 2017 - July 2021

Major: Software Enginer

WORK EXPERIENCE



VTech Group | May 2019 - Sep 2019

Research & Develop

Main responsibility:

- Researching on new technologies to develop products for the Company
- Research on Back-End, Database and system security.
- Support for checking system errors.
- -Develop Back-End



Rufa Technology | Sep 2019 - Dec 2020

Leader Team

Main responsibility:

- -Manage team members.
- -Support technical team.
- -Responsible for product release.
- Develop Front-End (Angular).
- Develop Back-End (C#).



TMA solutions | Jan 2021 - Now Senior Engineer

senior Enginee

Second Prize Mindx Grand Hackathon 2020

CERTIFICATIONS

2019

Google Analytics Individual Qualification

10-2020

Professional Front-End Developer Cybersoft Main responsibility:

- -Support technical team.
- -Develop Front-End (Reactjs, Angular).
- -Develop Back-End (C#, Java).
- -Tranning new member.

© topcv.vn